export const exercise1 = [

  		{
  		question:1,
  		exercise:"You learn Hausa?",
  		answer:"ka koya.  ",
  		subquestion:"Hausa"
  		},
  		{
  		question:2,
  		exercise:"Today is special",
  		answer:"Yau",
  		subquestion:"mahimi rana"
  		},
  		{
  		question:3,
  		exercise:"you are learning Hausa",
  		answer:"domin Zaka",
  		subquestion:"koya Hausa"
  		},
  		{
  		question:4,
  		exercise:"Good morning and good luck  ",
  		answer:"Barka da safe ",
      subquestion:"Allah ya bada sa’a"
  		},
  		{
  		question:5,
  		exercise:"Enjoy yourself",
  		answer:"Ji",
  		subquestion:"dadinka"
  		}

]
export const exercise2 = [
  {
  "question":1,
  "exercise":" Are you learning hausa? Yes",
  "answer":"ka koya. ",
  "subquestion":"Hausa? I"
},
  {
  "question":2,
  "exercise":" Good evening, are you alone?",
  "answer":"barka da yamma",
  "subquestion":"kai kade ne?"
  },
  {
  "question":3,
  "exercise":" yes, a room is free.I",
  "answer":"Akwai daki",
  "subquestion":"da ba kowa"
  },
  {
  "question":4,
  "exercise":"Blessing is alone",
  "answer":" Kade",
  "subquestion":"Blessing ita "
  },
  {
  "question":5,
  "exercise":"It cost £50",
  "answer":"Farashi sa",
  "subquestion":"£50"
  }
]
export const exercise3=[
  {
  "question":1,
  "exercise":"Joy is a friend of Caroline",
  "answer":"Joy ita kawan",
  "subquestion":"kawan Caroline"
  },
  {
  "question":2,
  "exercise":"who is Joy’s friend?",
  "answer":"Wanene",
  "subquestion":"kawan Joy?"
  },
  {
  "question":3,
  "exercise":"who is that?",
  "answer":"Wanene",
  "subquestion":"wannan?"
  },
  {
  "question":4,
  "exercise":"paul’s friend is called Richard",
  "answer":"Abokin Paul ",
  "subquestion":"ana kiran shi Richard"
  },
  {
  "question":5,
  "exercise":"Richard’s friend is called Joy",
  "answer":"abokin Richard.",
  "subquestion":"ana kiran ta joy"
  }
]
export const exercise5=[
  {
  "question":1,
  "exercise":"what do you want?",
  "answer":"Mai kake. ",
  "subquestion":"so?"
  },
  {
  "question":2,
  "exercise":"I would like  to have breakfast please",
  "answer":"Zan so",
  "subquestion":"so Karin kamallo"
  },
  {
  "question":3,
  "exercise":"Do you prefer coffee or tea?",
  "answer":"Zaka fi. ",
  "subquestion":"so kofi ko shayi?"
  },
  {
  "question":4,
  "exercise":" Here is the tea  and bread",
  "answer":"Ga. ",
  "subquestion":"shayi da burodi"
  },
  {
  "question":5,
  "exercise":"what is that? It is bread and meat",
  "answer":"Menene wannan",
  "subquestion":"burodi  da nama"
  }
]
